ED.
Yes.
Their relationship.
See, this is it.
This is it.
Shoulders like this.
Like this, like this.
Just the right height.
I'm one year older than you.
You are an idol.
But I feel like we are almost the same age.
But really, you don't look older than me.
You know, you don't look older than me.
I have wave arms, or rather, I have wave arms,
The other Yuzu and Hana-chan are two years younger than me,
I call them Harimaron.
They call me Harichan or Harimaron.
Chiho and Rumpan also call me Harimaron,
Even Moe, who is the same age as me, calls me Harimaron,
Even Moemi, who is the same age as me, calls me Harima, but it is Aryn and Ira who call me Harima.
Is it the same as Aryn's?
Yes.
That's right.
I thought everyone called him Harima,
Surprisingly, they don't.
But it's not Harimarron.
It's not Harichan.
I'm calling other people, so it's me.
It's Harima.
I'm Harima.
But I also call the loser Ira.
I call him Ira.
But, isn't there any other name than "Ira"?
There is a nickname "Ira-chan," but I don't know what else to call her,
I see.
Basically, I'm not good at calling people by their names,
I call Hari-chan "Chibiyuzu" too,
I can't call Hana-chan "Hana" either,
I call her Hana-chan because I can't call her Hana,
Rumpan is also called Rumpan,
Cho-chan is also called Cho-chan,
And when it's Arin, it's Arin,
So, Ira.
That's what I mean.
I don't like it when people's names are too long,
But you call me Harima,
So I thought I'd call you Harima too.
Is that what you mean?
Then let's both call each other that.
Let's call each other that.
OK.
You wanted to mount him, so I did it.
I was mounted.
Korea, I went to Korea,
You've been there.
It's an iramount, right?
That kind of thing.
I'm floating.
Even though I'm saying I want to go to Korea so badly.
Yeah. When I heard that,
I thought, "Okay, I'll go.
What's with that? You're a bad person.
Can I go?
I just wanted to show off.
Oh, I'm so excited!
But I got it from Harima for Korean use.
That's right. I gave it to her as a Korean gift,
Ira said he wanted to go to Starbucks in Korea,
I want to go there too.
So we went.
What did I just do?
I hadn't really decided on Korea, like where I wanted to go.
I guess I just wanted to go.
Ira is Ira is Ira is Ira.
So, I was like, "Ira said he wanted to go to Starbucks.
It's all Ira.
But he loves Ira.
He loves Ira.
I love her,
He's easy to mount.
Easy to mount.
Yes, it's easy to mount.
We have such a good relationship.
We get along really well.
Do I have anything to say?
Harima is Harima.
But earlier, when I was doing my makeup.
We were sitting next to each other,
We were talking all the time.
Even when I was talking to her, she was talking all the time.
I thought it was too loud.
No, no, no.
But Ira too.
Everyone in Amefras is talking backstage.
It's pretty loud.
Mount is the loudest.
But I once visited Amehras backstage,
Ira was talking all the time.
He was talking all by himself.I talk all the time alone.
I can't speak for others.
Rather than talking and talking, I'm talking by myself.
I'm talking by myself.
People are so big.
So maybe we are similar.
Maybe I am similar in that way.
Maybe we have something in common.
They call me a voice actor.
I am a voice actor. I'm still a 3D junior.
We're working together, and we're still working hard.
That's the thing.
I love it.
I like the idea of being a voice actor.
I am a voice actor.
Thank you.